

github.com/Aaron03-92



https://aaronsoggi.github.io

In linkedin.com/in/aaron-soggi



PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a conscientious, competent and committed individual with a strong foundation in software engineering and programming principles. Experience with software development- including planning and implementing different methodologies e.g., agile and scrum. I am able to demonstrate code maintenance, version control and testing. Capable of working independently or collaboratively to deliver beautiful products within specific deadlines. I am looking forward to applying the acquired gamut of skills in a challenging role.



EXPERIENCE

Hospital Management system

A .Net application purely using C# within Visual Studio 2019. The aim of the project was to create a system that would be suitable within a hospital environment, to keep patient data organised and manageable. The data was maintained through JSON text files.

Coach booking system

A windows form application which was created using Visual Studio 2019. The aim of the project was to create an executable solution of an online booking system, which manages the data through a RDBMS. Version control was executed on a weekly basis. I implemented SQL queries such as inserting, updating, removing, searching for related data and more.

Medulate

Medulate is a medical based application that I created in android studio. It includes a pills reminder and diary to help the user keep track of any monumental health concerns. Data was managed through google firebase i.e notes and login credentials. Both user and functionality testing was undertaken throughout the project.

Teesside University

Bachelor of Arts in Computer

Derby College/2011-2013Btech Diploma: Games

2013-2016

Games Design

Development

EDUCATION

- Nottingham Trent University 2020-present
 - MSc Computing systems Current grade - **Distinction**
- Software Engineering 1- First
- Systems Analysis and Design First
- Software Engineering 2 First
- Mobile Interactive Systems First
- Engineering Interactive Apps First
- Research Methods First

.

SKILLS

- C# SQL
- Java
 MySQL
- Python Android studio
- Unity Html
- Debugging
 CSS
- Tensorflow .Net Framework
- Github Agile software development
- Django ASP.NET Core

CONTACT

- (+44) 7943-477-455
- Aaron.soggi@outlook.com
- 606 Burton Road Littleover Derby DE23 6DH

HOBBIES







Fitness

Gaming





Music

Reading